export const data = {
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "How often do you find yourself using JavaScript in your web development projects?",
        "options": [
          "Rarely+0",
          "Occasionally+1",
          "Frequently+2",
          "Almost always+3"
        ],
        "correctOption": "Frequently"
      },
      {
        "question": "Do you tend to share your JavaScript knowledge and practices with others or prefer to keep it to yourself?",
        "options": [
          "Share with others+3",
          "Keep to myself+1",
          "Varies depending on the situation+2",
          "I'm not familiar with JavaScript+0"
        ],
        "correctOption": "Share with others"
      },
      {
        "question": "What motivates you the most to use JavaScript in your projects?",
        "options": [
          "Client-side interactivity and dynamic content+1",
          "Server-side development with Node.js+2",
          "Asynchronous programming and handling events+3",
          "Curiosity and exploration of JavaScript+0"
        ],
        "correctOption": "Curiosity and exploration of JavaScript"
      },
      {
        "question": "How would you describe your expertise level in using JavaScript for web development?",
        "options": [
          "Beginner+0",
          "Intermediate+1",
          "Advanced+2",
          "Expert+3"
        ],
        "correctOption": "Intermediate"
      },
      {
        "question": "Do you actively seek new JavaScript features, libraries, and best practices?",
        "options": [
          "Yes, regularly+0",
          "Sometimes+1",
          "Rarely+2",
          "No, not at all+3"
        ],
        "correctOption": "Yes, regularly"
      },
      {
        "question": "Have others sought your advice or expressed appreciation for your JavaScript knowledge?",
        "options": [
          "Yes, frequently+3",
          "Occasionally+2",
          "Rarely+1",
          "No, never+0"
        ],
        "correctOption": "Occasionally"
      },
      {
        "question": "Do you feel a sense of accomplishment after successfully implementing complex functionality using JavaScript?",
        "options": [
          "Always+0",
          "Sometimes+1",
          "Rarely+2",
          "Never+3"
        ],
        "correctOption": "Always"
      },
      {
        "question": "Have you participated in JavaScript-related workshops or sought professional certifications?",
        "options": [
          "Yes+0",
          "Considering it+1",
          "No, not yet+2",
          "No, and I don't plan to+3"
        ],
        "correctOption": "Yes"
      },
      {
        "question": "How would you rate the impact of JavaScript on your project's interactivity, functionality, and overall user experience?",
        "options": [
          "Low impact+0",
          "Moderate impact+1",
          "High impact+2",
          "Very high impact+3"
        ],
        "correctOption": "High impact"
      },
      {
        "question": "Do you believe that staying updated with JavaScript advancements is essential for modern web development?",
        "options": [
          "Strongly agree+0",
          "Agree+1",
          "Neutral+2",
          "Disagree+3"
        ],
        "correctOption": "Strongly agree"
      }
    ]
  }
  